[
  {
    "question": "vlinder",
    "answer": "schmetterling"
  },
  {
    "question": "ziekenauto",
    "answer": "ambulanz"
  },
  {
    "question": "balpen",
    "answer": "kugelschreiber"
  },
  {
    "question": "kerk",
    "answer": "kirche"
  },
  {
    "question": "zee",
    "answer": "meer"
  },
  {
    "question": "pannenkoek",
    "answer": "pfannkuchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "paarden",
    "answer": "pferde"
  },
  {
    "question": "woensdag",
    "answer": "mittwoch"
  },
  {
    "question": "fietsbel",
    "answer": "fahrradklingel"
  },
  {
    "question": "snor",
    "answer": "schnurrbart"
  },
  {
    "question": "blauw",
    "answer": "blau"
  },
  {
    "question": "hoofd",
    "answer": "kopf"
  },
  {
    "question": "lachen",
    "answer": "lachen"
  },
  {
    "question": "konijn",
    "answer": "kaninchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "voetbal",
    "answer": "fussbal"
  },
  {
    "question": "wijsvinger",
    "answer": "zeigefinger"
  },
  {
    "question": "schoon",
    "answer": "sauber"
  },
  {
    "question": "zon",
    "answer": "sonne"
  },
  {
    "question": "schoenen",
    "answer": "schuhe"
  },
  {
    "question": "broek",
    "answer": "hose"
  },
  {
    "question": "autobaan",
    "answer": "autobahn"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwembad",
    "answer": "schwimmbad"
  },
  {
    "question": "trein",
    "answer": "zug"
  },
  {
    "question": "schelden",
    "answer": "flugen"
  },
  {
    "question": "tafeltennis",
    "answer": "tischtennis"
  },
  {
    "question": "ontbijt",
    "answer": "fruhstuck"
  },
  {
    "question": "wereld",
    "answer": "welt"
  },
  {
    "question": "huis",
    "answer": "haus"
  },
  {
    "tools": "gratis",
    "answer": "kostenlos"
  },
  {
    "tools": "woordenboek",
    "answer": "wortenbuch"
  }
]













